

# **Haidar Dayoub**

+963 930935479 Male haydardayoub369@gmail.com 11. Jul.1995 Syria - Lattakia Syrian

### Summery

I am an experienced telecommunications engineer, whose experience extends to designing and developing frontend websites and applications. It built and improved user experiences, with a focus on making designs seamless and easy to use. Besides, she gained valuable experience in the field of accounting and data entry for 6 years, where she was involved in financial records management and financial reporting development using several well-known accounting software.

#### Skills

- Analytical thinking.
- Problem solving.
- Communication skills.
- Accuracy and attention to detail.
- Withstand working pressure.
- Manage time effectively.

- Flexibility and adaptability.
- Organize work and manage tasks effectively.
- Planning and organization.
- Teamwork.
- Accounting skills.
- Programming skills and interface design.

## **Work Experience**

## - Vica web solutions company for software solutions Developer Front End

2023 – Present Syria – Lattakia

- Analyze customer requirements and determine their user interface needs.
- Using the framework (bootstrap)
- Use (React JS) technology.
- Create projects using (vite webpack.)
- Convert interface designs into executable code using (HTML, CSS, and JavaScript).
- Ensure that interfaces are compatible with different browsers and devices.
- Collaborate with the back-end development team to ensure the integration of the interfaces with the overall system.
- Testing and debugging interfaces.
- Follow security and privacy standards in the design and development of facades.
- Document the development process and provide the necessary reports to the management team and customers.

#### - Odila Pharma For Pharmaceutical Industries Data Entry

2021 - 2023

Syria – Lattakia

- Enter data accurately and quickly in the selected database system using Al-Ameen program.
- Ensure that the entered data is correct and ensure that there are no errors.
- Organize and classify files and documents in an organized and appropriate manner.
- Handling data related queries and needs by colleagues and customers.
- Maintain the confidentiality and security of the entered data.

#### - Afamia Rotana Resort (Cafe 360) accountant

2018 -2019

Syria – Lattakia

- Manage all general accounting processes using infinity software.
  - Carry out daily and monthly accounting operations.
  - Manage and track all financial movements and update purchase and sales records.
  - Maintain the confidentiality of financial statements.
  - Archiving and organizing financial operations and organizing them in an easy way.

- Orange Mall (Pascochi Cafe)

accountant

2016 –2018 Syria – Lattakia

 Carrying out daily and monthly accounting operations for the café using the Omega accounting program.

- Monitor and review accounting records.
- Manage day-to-day financial operations, such as preparing customer invoices and following up on payments and expenses.
- Communicate effectively with the management team and employees.

#### - Syrian Telecom Company

2016 - 2017

#### **Technical Engineer**

Syria – Lattakia

- Installation and maintenance of communication and networking equipment.
- Provide technical support and solve technical problems for customers and employees.
- Modernization of telecommunications infrastructure.
- Providing technical advice to customers and the company.
- Carry out tests and evaluations of communication systems to ensure their optimal performance.
- Training employees on the use of communication devices and modern technologies.
- Provide technical reports and statistics to the company's management.

#### **Education**

- Bachelor's degree

2020

 Communications and Electronics Engineering Tishreen University Syria – Lattakia

#### **COMPUTER SKILLS**

- Excellent mastery of work on office programs (Microsoft Office).
- Communication tools (e-mail, Internet).
- Accounting Trustee Program.
- Infinity accounting software.
- Omega accounting software.
- HTML, CSS, JavaScript

## Other Strength

- Having a positive working attitude.
- Very enthusiastic and dedicated.
- Good interacting skill.
- Commitment to work with a high level of confidence.
- The ability to distribute attention to more than one task at a time (multitasking).
- Accuracy in preparing reports and delivering them on time.
- Attention to detail, ability to solve problems and act under pressure.
- Customerservice.

## Language

- Arabic: Mother tongue.
- English: Very good.